Guide to the Association of Yale Alumni Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1951-2005; 1979-1995; Accession 2015-A-030
  - AYA Assembly
    - Assembly XXI: Dedication and re-dedication, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - Assembly XXIII
      - Board of Governor's meeting, 1983 Fall (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Division I alumni communications, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Division II committees, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Division II memberhip development, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Residential college report, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Assembly XXIX
      - University environment: perspectives on Yale's facilities, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Info session minutes, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Assembly XXX
      - Club Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Interdisciplinary and special programs, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Info-session minutes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Assembly XXXI
      - Club Committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - The faculty at Yale, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Follow-up memo, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Info-session minutes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Assembly XXXII
      - The arts at Yale, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Club Committee mailings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Info-session minutes, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Post-assembly letters to YC presidents, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Assembly XXXIII
      - Info-session minutes, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Sandra Bialos mailing, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Assembly XXXIV: Social, community and extra-curricular activities at Yale, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Assembly XXXV: Health care programs at Yale, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Assembly XXXVI
      - Commitment to public service, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Friday core group luncheon, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Info-session minutes, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Yale historical and contemporary, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Assembly XXXVIII: Inventing the future: scholarly research at Yale today, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Assembly XLVII: Athletics at Yale, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Board of Governors
    - A and E Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Accreditation and Election Committee: Dan Nugent, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Alumni fellows correspondence (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Fellows mailings for 1987, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3a)
    - Alumni Fellows Nominating Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Alumni fellows nominations, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Alumni fellows photographs, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Alvin N. Puryear correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - AYA board, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - AYA board of governors workshop, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - AYA committees, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - AYA constitution and by-laws, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
    - AYA vacancy letters, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Board election: Chair and Vice-Chair, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Board luncheon speakers, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Board meetings
      - 1980 June (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - 1980 September (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - 1980 October (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - 1981 January (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - 1981 March (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - 1981 May (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - 1981 September (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - 1981 October (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - 1983 February (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - 1983 April (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - 1983 June (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - 1983 October (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - 1983 December (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - 1984 February (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - 1984 April (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - 1984 June (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - 1984 October (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - 1984 December (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - 1985 February (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - 1985 June (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - 1985 December (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - 1986 February (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - 1986 June (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - 1986 October (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - 1986 December (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - 1987 February (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - 1987 April (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - 1987 June (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - 1987 October (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - 1987 December (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - 1988 February (Box 8, Folder 19)
        General
        Includes club workshop notes
      - 1988 April (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - 1988 June (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - 1988 November (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - 1988 December (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - 1989 April (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - 1989 June (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - 1989 October (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - 1989 December (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - 1990 February (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - 1990 April (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - 1990 October (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Board of Governors correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Board of Governors Nominating Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Board of Governors Nominating Committee ballots, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Board of Governors Nominating Committee elections, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Board of Governors nominations, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Club president workshop, 1988 February (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Club Committee chairs, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Club Committee on Alumni Schools, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Club Committee on Athletics, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Club Committee on Finance, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Club Committee on Information, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Club Committee on Service to Classes, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Club Committee on Student Life, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Committee on the Arts, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Committee on the Constitution, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Committee liasion, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Committee members, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Committee reports, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Committee on undergraduate admissions, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Committee to nominate Chair, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Committees, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15a)
    - Committees-general, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Committees-nominations, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence with Board of Governors, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Delegate letters re: Fall Assembly, 1988 September (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Election-general, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Election for Board of Governors, 1982 October (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Election for representatives, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Former AYA Boards of Governors, 1983-1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Kelly, John F.-general file, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Kelly, John F.-correspondence to the Board of Governors, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
    - Liasion correspondence, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Levine, Howard correspondence, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Lipsher, Harry M.-correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Lipsher, Harry M.-meetings, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Members at-large, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - New AYA structure, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Nominations-Board of Governors, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 33-35)
    - Potential alumni fellow information, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Representatives at-large
      - 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
      - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Elections
        - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
        - 1984 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
      - Vacancies, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Yale Medal Committee
      - General files
        - 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
        - 1987 (Box 10, Folder 16)
        - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
        - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Carryovers dropped for 1997, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Citations, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Dinner, 1996 April (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Letters, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Luncheon, 1985 April (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Mailings, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Nomination forms, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Nominations, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
      - Nominees, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Nominees-correspondence, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Notebook materials, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Previous nominees, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Yale College classes
    - Class of 1926 and 1926S Executive Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1928 Day at Farmington, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1928 Yale/Harvard luncheon, 1983 November (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Classes of 1928, 1929 and 1945 luncheon at Coxe Cage, 1984 November (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1936, 1998-2005 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Class of 1937 luncheon, 1986 February (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Classes of 1938 and 1939 dinner, 1984 January (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Classes of 1938 and 1939 hockey dinner, 1983 February (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1940 hockey dinner, 1983 February (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1940 luncheon, 1984 January (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Class of 1941 Executive Council minutes, 1951-1986 (Box 11, Folder 25-27)
    - Class of 1941 30th reunion, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Class of 1941 35th reunion, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Class of 1941 40th reunion, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Classes of 1941, 1942, and 1943 hockey dinner, 1982 February (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Classes of 1941, 1942, 1943 dinner, 1984 February (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Classes of 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944 Harvard hockey dinner, 1985 February (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1945W hockey dinner, 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Class of 1945W hockey dinner, 1985 February (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Class of 1945W dinner, 1984 February (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Classes of 1946, 1947, 1948 dinner, 1983 November (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Classes of 1946, 1947, 1948 dinner, 1984 January (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Classes of 1946, 1947, 1948, 1949 hockey dinner, 1985 January (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Classes of 1946-1949 dinner, 1984 November (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Classes of 1950, 1951, 1952 hockey dinner, 1983 January (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Classes of 1950, 1951, 1952 hockey dinner, 1985 January (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Classes of 1950, 1951, 1952 dinner, 1984 January (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Class of 1951: Two-Days at Yale program, 1985 April (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Class of 1955 dinner, 1984 November (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Classes of 1955 and 1957 dinner, 1983 November (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1956 dinner, 1983 November (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1956 dinner, 1984 November (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Class of 1959 hockey dinner, 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1959 tent gathering, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Classes of 1961, 1962, 1963, 1964 dinner, 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Classes of 1961-1966 hockey dinner, 1985 February (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Classes of 1962-1966 hockey dinner, 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Classes of 1963, 1964 hockey dinner, 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1963 reunion, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 24-25)
    - Class of 1963 class day, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Classes of 1965-1968 dinner, 1984 February (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1966 hockey dinner, 1984 February (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Classes of 1970-1983 post-game parties (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Hockey dinners-general file, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Hockey dinners-general file, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Reunions, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Yale clubs
    - General file, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 32a)
    - Yale club of Alabama, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Yale club of Arizona, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Yale club associations and financial aid, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Yale club of California, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
    - Yale club of Colorado, 1975-1980 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Yale club of Connecticut, 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
    - Yale club of Delaware, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Yale club of the District of Columbia, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Yale club of Florida, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Yale club of Georgia, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Yale club of Hawaii, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Yale club of Illinois (Chicago), 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Yale club of Indiana, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Yale club of Iowa, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Yale club of Kansas, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Yale club of Kentucky, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Yale club of Louisiana, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Yale club of Maine, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Yale club of Maryland, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Yale clubs-officer's workshops, 1976-1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Yale club presidents, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Advisory board meeting minutes, 1906-1971; Accession 2016-A-009
  - Minutes, 1908-1938 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1938-1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1959-1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Meeting minutes ledgers and audio-visual materials, 1965-1996; Accession 2016-A-035
  - Meeting Minute Ledgers
    Records are restricted until January 1, 2051 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation.
    - Yale Association of Class Officers, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Board of Governors
      - 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1982-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Audio-Visual Materials
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies (designated by a box with a 'U' suffix), or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - One-inch video reels
      - New Haven Update, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Short Master, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Social Sciences (Yale), 1986 (Box 5)
      - Undergraduate Colleges (Yale), 1986 (Box 6)
      - Undergraduate Colleges (Yale), 1986 (Box 7)
      - Yale Engineering: The Undergraduate Experience, 1987 (Box 8)
    - PAL Video Cassettes
      - New Haven Update, 1984 (Box 9)
      - Yale's Undergraduate Colleges, 1984 (Box 10)
      - The Inquiring Mind-Science at Yale, 1986 (Box 11)
      - Yale Engineering: The Undergraduate Experience, 1987 (Box 12)
      - Yale Social Sciences, 1987 (Box 13)
- AYA Assembly records, 1998; Accession 2018-A-0009
  The materials are open for research.
  - Correspondence and event ephemera, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional Material, 1970-2006; Accession 2018-A-0044
  Restricted until January 1, 2042.
  - General Files
    - Report to the Yale Alumni on Alumni Activities, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, letters of intent, memoranda (phase I)-Rose Alumni House renovations, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Letters of Solicitation to class and club officers (phase II) Rose Alumni House renovations, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - AYA Staff photos, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Yale Fence photos (section at Rose Alumni House), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Yale University Arts & Sciences Reunion, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Association of Yale Alumni Assembly
    - Assembly IV: "Student Life at Yale" - photos, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
    - Assembly VI: "Yale's Graduate and Professional Schools"-photos, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
    - AYA Assembly Convocation 1976 – photos, 1975
      Material not received from office.
    - Assembly XXV: "The Social Sciences at Yale"-photos, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Assembly XXVIII: "Athletics at Yale: Education and Recreation" – Yale Medal Recipients – photos, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Assembly XXVIII: "Athletics at Yale: Education and Recreation", 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Assembly XXIX: "The University Environment: Perspectives on Yale's Facilities", 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Assembly XXX: "Interdisciplinary and Special Programs: Educational Diversity at Yale" – Yale Medal Recipients – photos, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Assembly XXXI: "The Faculty at Yale: Teaching, Research and Impact on the Outside World" – photos, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - Assembly XXXI: "The Faculty at Yale: Teaching, Research and Impact on the Outside World", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Assembly XXXI: "The Faculty at Yale: Teaching, Research and Impact on the Outside World" - information sessions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Assembly XXXII: "The Arts at Yale" – Yale Medal Recipients – photos, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Assembly XXXIV: "Social, Community and Extra-Curricular Activities at Yale" – Information Sessions, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Assembly XXXV: "Health Care Programs at Yale", 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Assembly XXXV: "Health Care Programs at Yale"-information session, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Assembly XXXVI: "Yale's Historical and Contemporary Commitment to Public Service" – Information Sessions, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Assembly XXXVII: "Contemporary Yale: Inventing the Future" – Information Sessions, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Assembly XXXVIII: "Yale and the Environment" –Information Sessions, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Assembly XXXIX: "The Internationalization of Yale"– Information Sessions, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Assembly XXXIX: "The Internationalization of Yale" – Post-Assembly Mailing, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Assembly XL: "20/200 Alumni and Yale: Perspectives and Challenges" – Information Sessions, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Assembly XL: "20/200 Alumni and Yale: Perspectives and Challenges" – Post-Assembly Mailing, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Assembly XLVIII: "Yale as an Environment for Learning" – Information Sessions, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Assembly XLVIII: "Yale as an Environment for Learning" – Post Assembly Mailing, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Assembly XLVIV: "Lux et Veritas: The Role of Light at Yale" – Information Sessions, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Assembly XLVI: "New Haven/New Yale/New Directions" – Post-Assembly Mailing, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Assembly XLVII: "Mens Sana in Corpore Sano: Athletics at Yale" – Post-Assembly Mailing, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Assembly XLVIII: "Admissions: Selection for Leadership" – Information Sessions, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Assembly L: "The Graduate School: Reflections on the Past and the Future" – Post-Assembly Mailing, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Association of Yale Alumni Board of Governors-meeting, 1994 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Commission on Alumni Affairs-Papers of Brian A. Moran, Executive Director, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
  - Yale College Classes
    - Class of 1928, 1988-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1929, 1989-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Class of 1929-support for Timothy Dwight Library, 1996-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Class of 1930, 1998-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Class of 1931, 1980-2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Class of 1932, 1989-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Class of 1933, 1989-2006 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Class of 1934, 1989-2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1935, 1989-2006 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
    - Class of 1959, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Class of 1960, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1961, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1962, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1963, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
    - Class of 1964, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Class of 1965, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1966, 1988-1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1967, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Class of 1968, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Class of 1969, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1970, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1971, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1972, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Class of 1973, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Class of 1974, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Yale College Reunions
    - Programs from the Classes of 1968, 1973, 1978, 1983, and 1988, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Class of 1929 65th reunion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Class of 1934 60th reunion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Class of 1939 55th reunion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Class of 1944 50th reunion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1949 45th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1954 40th reunion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Class of 1959 35th reunion, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1964 30th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Class of 1969 25th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Class of 1930 65th reunion, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Class of 1935 60th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1940 55th reunion, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1945 50th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Class of 1945W 50th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Class of 1950 45th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Class of 1955 40th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1960 35th reunion, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1965 30th reunion, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Class of 1970 25th reunion, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Class of 1975 20th reunion, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1980 15th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1985 10th reunion, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1990 5th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Multi class programs, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Directories, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Reunion workshop, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - General reunion orders, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Children of Yale, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Class of 1931 65th reunion, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Class of 1936 60th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Class of 1941 55th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Class of 1946 50th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Class of 1946 50th reunion class book, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Class of 1951 45th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Class of 1956 40th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Class of 1961 35th reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Class of 1966 30th reunion, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Class of 1971 25th reunion, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Class of 1976 20th reunion, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Class of 1981 15th reunion, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Class of 1986 10th reunion, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1991 5th reunion, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Reunion programs, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Reunion directories, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Children of Yale University, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Clerks, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Class of 1932 65th reunion, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Class of 1937 60th reunion, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Class of 1942 55th reunion, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Class of 1947 50th reunion, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Class of 1947 50th reunion photo orders, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Class of 1952 45th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1957 40th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1962 35th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Class of 1967 30th reunion, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Class of 1972 25th reunion, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)